William Hatcher
○ 5061 Hidden Lake Trl., Midlothian TX, 76065
② 262-563-9272
☑ william@hatcher.work

## ♠ PROFILE

I cannot easily be put into few words. People note my dedication, my love of food, the loyalty I show to friends, and my exceptional customer service. I have ample experience in food service not because it was the only job available, but because I love it! At the end of the day, good food needs to be in happy customers' stomachs, and I'm here to do the best job doing that.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Fuzzy's Taco Shop

2018 - Current

## Team Member

Responsible for expediting the best tacos around, with the best in customer service, and keeping the dishes clean with a mirror-shine finish.

## Kroger Marketplace

2017 - Current

### **Associate**

Responsible for conditioning aisles, stocking product, giving customers great service, and making sure things get done.

# Whataburger 2016 - 2017

### Team Leader Assistant

Responsible for correctly taking customers' orders, providing excellent customer service, and assisting managers in training employees.

# Jack in the Box 2015 - 2016

### Team Leader Assistant

Responsible for training new employees, relaying customer's orders to the kitchen, assisting managers in running the store, and, of course, giving the best in customer service.

#### **EDUCATION**

Current	Associates of Education	Navarro College
2016	Diploma	Midlothian High School

### **★** REFERENCES

Carter McClung, Teacher, MHHS	214-507-6062
Shala Beverly, Manager, Whataburger	972-775-2323
Debbie Munro, Manager, Lighthouse Cafe	682-802-8880